what this means one thing at a time
means one thing at a time you have what
we call variables a variable is every
element that can be impacted or
controlled frequency is a variable dose
is a
variable Esther is a
variable carrier oil is a variable all
of these variables are variables that
when we say change one at a time one at
a time don't change dose and frequency
now this is not a golden rule to abide
by by everyone for example if I see
someone come back with a low s
hpg and a very low level of total and or
free
testosterone then we may change more
than one variable we may increase their
frequency and also increase the dose at
the same time because we know that
change is coming anyway so with the vast
amount of experience of doing this
literally probably over 10,000 times now
with patients over the years we can
pretty much guess pretty well at this
point uh based on anecdotal experience
what this individual is going to need so
rather than making one change and then
three months later making a second
change and taking six months to reach
our destination we may make two changes
at once in order to reach that
destination sooner because we kind of
already have an idea of how they are
going to respond with that said if you
have or if your provider has has the
experience you as an individual you'll
never have the level of experience of a
provider who's done this with thousands
of patients but if your provider has the
experience and know how then they may
change more than one variable at a time
but ideally if unsure it is always safer
to take baby steps because here's the
thing you make two changes and something
goes sideways now you don't know why you
have to undo both and you're going back
to square one whereas if you made one
change at a time and it didn't go well
you can pinpoint that that the root
cause presumably so that's why we say
one at a time it just makes it easier to
dial in